

Pieter Bikkel

Full Stack Developer

Vorden, Netherlands

+31 6 16 46 01 71

pieterbikkel.com

Summary.

Software developer with years of experience in Design, development, testing, and maintenance of various Enterprise Web and Mobile Applications. Supportive and enthusiastic team player dedicated to streamlining the process and efficiently resolving project issues. Demonstrating the ability to learn and adapt quickly to new technologies. Extremely end customer focused with excellent verbal communication skills that allow understanding and aligning with customer's goals and expectations. Experienced working in high-pressure environments delivering and maintaining mission-critical systems. Demonstrated ability to work independently and undertake research to find an ideal solution for a complex problem in a defined time frame.

Work experience

Software Developer

2020-12 - Present

B302

- Maintaining Dutch government iOS apps for the public healthcare.
- Building a new React application for the police and ambulance to audit calls.
- Building a new Study Abroad React application for the HAN, University of applied sciences.

IT configuration management

2018-06 - Present

Bronkhorst High-Tech

• Configuring, replacing and wiping computers for users within the company.

Education

Bachelor Of Science In Software Engineering

2020-09 - Present

HAN, University of applied sciences

Subjects Covered

- Networks
- Databases
- Data Structures
- Software Design
- Interface Design

- Web Technologies
- Operating Systems
- Software Engineering
- Security and Encryption
- Software Project Management

Senior General Secondary Education, **Nature & Technology**

Baudartius College

English

 Dutch • Mathematics for scientific studies

· Advanced mathematics

Computer Science

Physics

Chemistry

Skills —

Build Systems

Jenkins

Maven

Version Control Systems

Git

Code Hosting Services

Github

Bitbucket

Gitlab

Operating Systems

macOS

Windows

• Linux (Ubuntu)

Google Workspace

Office Suite

• iWork

Microsoft Office

Databases

MongoDB

MSSQL

MySQL

Neo4i

Programming Languages

Objective-C

Javascript

 Swift Java

Development /

Environment Tools

Xcode

• PHP

MS Visual Studio

Intellij IDEA

• Figma

Azure data studio

Zeplin

Generic Development Skills

Networking

Unit Testing

· Code Reviews

Virtualization

Cloud Services

Source Control

Data Structures

· Algorithm Design

Operating Systems

· Agile Methodologies

· Object-oriented Design

Continuous Integration

· Planning and Estimation

• Open Source Contribution